We're almost done styling our ad entry view,
添加条目视图的样式快设置完毕了
there are just a few notable changes that we need to make.
还需要进行几项明显的更改
One is our slider right here as well as the metrics below it.
一个是这里的滑块 以及下面的指标
Our date and then also,
还有日期
we need to style our reset button right here.
还需要对这里的 reset 按钮设置样式
So let's go ahead and get started on that.
我们开始设置吧
First, let's do the DateHeader since that's a pretty small one.
首先 设置 DateHeader 样式 因为内容很少
What we will do is,
我们将在这里
let's just go ahead and add an inline style here.
添加一个内嵌样式
We'll give it a color of purple which we will import here in a second,
color 设为 purple 稍后导入 purple
and we will say fontSize 25.
fontSize 设为 25
So now, we will import purple.
现在导入 purple
This is coming from utils dot colors.
来自于 ../utils/colors
So now, notice this is nice and styled, our DateHeader.
DateHeader 样式设置好了
Next, let's go ahead and do our slider which is located in UdaciSlider.
接着设置滑块样式 转到 UdaciSlider.js 文件
So first, what we need to do is import
首先 我们需要导入 StyleSheet
StyleSheet and we will also import gray from our colors.
还需要导入 gray 来自 colors
So what we want to do here is we want to have these items be laid out in a row,
我们希望这些项水平排列
like we've talked about with the other components as well.
就像其他组件那样
So what we can do is create a style sheet,
创建一个 StyleSheet
give it a row property,
设置 row 属性
which will set the main flexDirection to be row,
将主 flexDirection 设为 row
flex 1 again and then alignItems in the center.
再次输入 flex: 1 alignItems 设为 center
And then, we'll use metricCounter again as we've done before,
然后像之前一样使用 metricCounter
we'll give it a width of 85.
将 width 设为 85
And then we will justify the content along
然后将 justifyContent 设为 center
the center as well as alignItems along the center.
并将 alignItems 设为 center
So now, all we need to do is we will come up here,
现在转到这里
and we will apply our metricCounter to this view right here.
对此 View 应用 metricCounter
To this view, we will apply styles.row,
对此 View 应用 styles.row
and then we will give some inline styles to these two text components.
然后对这两个 Text 组件设置一些内嵌样式
Say, fontSize of 24,
fontSize 设为 24
textAlign center, and something similar here.
textAlign 设为 center 这里也是类似的设置
We will say fontSize of 18 and then a color of gray.
fontSize 设为 18 color 设为 gray
Now, you may have noticed that this section,
你可能会发现 在这部分
and specifically these styles,
具体而言 是这些样式
are very similar to what we did in our Steppers file.
与我们在 UdaciSteppers 文件中的设置非常相似
If you wanted to consolidate these,
如何你想整合这些样式
you could make a single object somewhere and just
可以在某个位置设置一个对象
import that into both of these components,
然后向这两个组件中导入该对象
and then you would basically not be duplicating the styles here.
这样就不用重复设置这些样式
I'm not a huge fan of that just because I feel like eventually,
我不太喜欢这么做
if we need to change one of them,
因为最终如果你想更改其中一个的样式
we would have to then, decouple those.
还需要拆开来
But again, it's up to you.
当然看你喜欢哪种方式了
So what we want to do with our slider,
对于滑块
you'll notice that it's not taking up the full space of it's parents.
你会发现它没有占用父组件的整个空间
So to fix that, what we can do is we can come in here and give this a flex of one.
要解决该问题 我们转到这里 并输入 flex: 1
So that's why I keep talking about whenever you have,
这就是为何我一直提到
or whenever you want a component to take up the full space of its parent,
每当你希望某个组件占用父组件的整个空间时
you need to give it a flex of one,
需要将 flex 设为 1
which will now make it look like this.
之后 效果就会变成这样
So, that looks great.
看起来不错
The very last thing we need to do is just style this reset button right here,
最后我们需要对这里的 Reset 按钮设置样式
that is located inside of TextButton,
它位于 TextButton 中
so what we do is we're going to need the color purple,
我们需要导入 purple
and let's also go ahead and import StyleSheet while we're here.
趁机在这里导入 StyleSheet
We'll create some styles,
我们将创建一些样式
let's say, we'll have a reset property.
设置 property 属性
And what we're going to do is we'll say textAlign center,
将 textAlign 设为 center
we could have just inline these but we'll go ahead and use StyleSheet for this.
我们可以内嵌这些样式 但是我们使用 StyleSheet 吧
Color is going to be purple,
color 设为 purple
and then up here,
然后在这里
what we're going to do is we're going to say style is going to equal styles.reset,
将 style 设为 styles.reset
and eventually, what I want to be able to do is
最终 我希望在这里
I want to be able to pass in Styles as a prop.
能够将 style 当做属性导入
So what we'll do is we'll say,
因此
if styles undefined, set it equal to an empty object.
如果 style 是 undefined 则设为空的对象
But instead of just applying styles.reset,
不仅要应用 styles.reset
I also want to be able to apply style,
我还希望能够应用 style
which is coming from the prop again.
也来自这个属性
So now, just one small change real quick,
快速修正下
that's going to be./utils.
这里应该是 ../utils
And so now, if we look at this view,
现在看看视图效果
you'll notice our reset button is nice and styled and we can go ahead and click it.
你会发现 Reset 按钮样式设置好了 我们可以点击它